Long Live Evil
Descendants 2 is a family, fantasy, tv movie film directed by Kenny Ortega.
When the pressure to be royal becomes too much for Mal, she returns to the Isle of the Lost where
her archenemy Uma, Ursula's daughter, has taken her spot as self-proclaimed queen.
Mal, played by Dove Cameron.
Ben, played by Mitchell Hope.
Carlos, played by Cameron Boyce.
Evie, played by Sofia Carson.
Harry, played by Thomas Doherty.
Chad Charming, played by Jedidiah Goodacre.
Descendants 2 is an American musical fantasy
television film directed by Kenny Ortega.
It is a sequel to Descendants (2015), and the second
installment in the Descendants franchise.
The film stars Dove Cameron, Cameron Boyce, Sofia Carson, Booboo
Stewart, Mitchell Hope, and China Anne McClain.
It premiered as a Disney Channel Original Movie on July 21, 2017, and was simulcast on
Disney-owned networks ABC, Disney XD, Freeform, Lifetime, and Lifetime Movies.
It was followed by a third film, Descendants 3,
which premiered on August 2, 2019.
The film explores themes of magic, fairy tale, villain, musical, teen movie.